Guide to the Social Democratic Federation of America Records TAM.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Social Democratic Federation of America Records
1933-1956
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Social Democratic Federation of America
TAM.011
6.5 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
The Social Democratic Federation of America (SDF) was organized in 1936 after the split in the Socialist Party between the Old Guard and the Militants. It was able to attract many of the traditional Socialist Party sources of support and its activities were directed by many prominent Socialist Party members, including August Claessens, Algernon Lee, Leo Meltzer, James Oneal and Louis Waldman. The SDF sought to promote the principles of social democracy and independent political action. In the late 1930's, SDF was associated with the American Labor Party of New York and the People's Party. During the 1940's and early 1950's, SDF's membership and influence declined forcing merger negotiations with the Socialist Party. The merger was affected in 1957. Contains correspondence with state branches; records of the national office and national executive committee; extensive records (1936-1956) of the New York City local, including correspondence, minutes, and financial records; material on Jewish Socialist Verband, Camp Tamiment (Pa.), the Fred Beal case, which grew out of the 1919 strike in Gastonia, N.C., WEVD (1933-1935) and various committees formed by the federation; also includes clippings on Jasper McLevy, national chairman.
Custodial History
This collection was transferred to NYU in 1963 from the Tamiment Institute Library. There is no earlier provenace information about this collection. The accession number 1963.018 is associated with this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Social Democratic Federation of America (SDF) was organized in 1936 after the split in the Socialist Party ranks between the Old Guard and the Militants. Although not an official political party like the Socialist Party, the SDF was a political organization which consisted of the following groups: (1) Socialist Party state branches, particularly those in New York, Connecticut, Pennsylvania, and Maryland; (2) Socialist Party municipal locals, particularly those in Reading, Pennsylvania, under the leadership of James H. Maurer, and Bridgeport, Connecticut, under the leadership of Mayor Jasper McLevy; (3) labor parties, especially members of the American Labor Party of New York, the FarmerLabor Party of Minnesota, and the Non Partisan League; and (4) socialist foreign language organizations, like the Jewish Socialist Verband and the Finnish Socialist Federation. During its formative period, the SDF was not only able to attract many of the traditional Socialist Party sources of financial support, but its activities were also directed by many prominent members of the Socialist Party, including August Claessens, Algernon Lee, Leo Meltzer, James Oneal, and Louis Waldman.
During its 20 year history, the SDF sought to promote the principles of social democracy and independent political action. Such ideals were realized through a variety of activities concerning domestic and international issues. Regarding the domestic issues, the SDF sought legislation to amend the National Labor Relations Act, supported Franklin D. Roosevelt in his Presidential campaigns in 1940 and 1944, called upon all labor organizations to unite against communist groups in the United States, and endorsed civil rights legislation. Internationally, the SDF played a vital role in various programs that brought German refugee children to the United States. The SDF also supported American participation in World War II, opposed Mahatma Gandhi's independence movement in India during the war, and assisted in the relocation of Jewish refugees after the war.
Like the Socialist Party, the SDF was also plagued by bitter internal conflicts. One of the major controversies affecting the organization in the late 1930s and early 1940s was its relationship with the American Labor Party of New York. When the New York Old Guard became the New York State division of the SDF in 1936, they adopted the name "People's Party" and subsequently joined the American Labor Party. From the perspective of the People's Party, this linkage with the American Labor Party was seen as an opportunity to help organize a formidable labor party, support Franklin D. Roosevelt in his Presidential reelection bid, and still remain outside the realm of conventional party politics. Ironically, however, the members of the People's Party, who had earlier withdrawn from the Socialist Party on the grounds that it was overly sympathetic towards communism, were now closely associated with an organization which was controlled by communists. The unsettling relationship with the American Labor Party ultimately caused such influential SDF figures as Louis Waldman and Leo Meltzer to resign from the organization.
Another conflict within the SDF involved the New Leader and its editor, James Oneal. Shortly after the SDF was established in the fall of 1936, the editorial board of the New Leader withdrew its support for the Socialist Party and joined the new organization. The relationship between the New Leader staff and the SDF executive committee was never cordial, since both groups held differing opinions as to what the editorial policy of the newspaper should be. These disagreements became so large in scope and so emotional in tone that James Oneal finally resigned as editor in 1940. In his resignation letter, Oneal stated that the New Leader had become a liberal, progressive publication instead of a significant SDF organ and that the New Leader had failed to strengthen the SDF overall. Following Oneal's resignation, the editorial board of the New Leader and the SDF leadership continued to fight over the proper editorial policy for the publication. Eventually, the staff of the New Leader split from the SDF.
During the 1940s and early 1950s, the SDF experienced a drastic decline in its membership and influence. Much of this decline can be attributed to three major factors: (1) the general decline in the popularity of socialism throughout this period; (2) the movement of many socialists, social democrats, and progressive liberals into the Americans for Democratic Action and other liberal organizations; and (3) the suspicions generated by the SDF's association with the American Labor Party. By the early 1950s, this decline forced the SDF leadership to begin serious negotiations with the Socialist Party on a possible merger. Attempts at uniting these two organizations began as early as 1937 and continued through the 1940s without much success. At this point in time, however, the mutual decline of both organizations had prompted a reassessment of the merger issue. Finally, in 1957, after several years of negotiations, the SDF merged with the Socialist Party.
Scope and Content Note
The Social Democratic Federation of America Records, 1933 1956, consist of 89 files (some containing more than one folder), organized into nine series. Each file has been given a microfilm frame number. In the representative frame number (X:1), the arabic numeral "1" indicates that this is the first file, while the roman numeral "X" indicates that the SDF Records are the tenth collection in the microfilm publication Socialist Collections in the Tamiment Library, 1872-1956.
The materials contained in this collection include correspondence, financial papers, minutes, resolutions, ephemeral printed matter, reports, press releases, memoranda, lists, ballots, statements, position papers, political platforms, form letters, and circular letters. Each subject file within these sections has been assigned a frame number. Both the sections and the subject files have been cited in the complete reel list which follows this description of the arrangement of the collection.
Arrangement
Correspondence folders are arranged chonologically, the remainder, alphabetically.
Arranged in nine series:
Missing Title
I. National files
II. State and International Files
III. Jewish Socialist Verband Files
IV. Committee Files
V. Financial Files
VI. Literature Files
VII. New York City Files
VIII. New York State Files
IX. Miscellaneous (not microfilmed).
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Socialist Collections in the Tamiment Library, 1872-1956 (Tamiment Microfilm: Film R-7124)
Socialist Collections in the Tamiment Library, 1872-1956: a Guide to the Microfilm Edition.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of the original materials, researchers must use the microfilmed version; microfilm call number is Film R-7124, Reels 15-18. Series IX is not availbale on microfilm.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The provenance of this collection is unknown. The accession number associated with this collection is 1963.018.
Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Account books.; Minutes (administrative records); Textile Workers' Strike, Gastonia, N.C., 1929.; Beal Case.; Labor unions -- United States.; Socialists -- United States.; McLevy, Jasper.; Maurer, James.; Beal, Fred Erwin, 1896-1954; Debs, Theodore, 1864-1945; Socialist Party (U.S.); Jewish Socialist Verband; Claessens, August, 1885-1954; WEVD (Radio station) New York, N.Y.; Social Democratic Youth; New leader (New York, N.Y.: 1924); People's Party (N.Y.); American Labor Party; Lee, Algernon; Oneal, James, 1875-1962; Russell, Charles Edward, 1860-1941; Meltzer, Leo.; Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942.; Waldman, Louis, b. 1892; Lewis, Lena Morrow; Socialist Party-Social Democratic Federation
- Series I. National Files
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains considerable correspondence pertaining to a variety of SDF affairs and the first SDF convention held at Pittsburgh in 1937. The items within each of these five files are arranged in chronological order. The bulk of the national correspondence (X:l, X:2) pertains to such routine SDF matters as scheduling meetings and special events, receiving dues, resolving membership problems, handling literature requests, and organizing fund raising campaigns. Besides these routine items, the correspondence also contains information on the Socialist Party split in 1936, the controversial alliance between the SDF and the American Labor Party, the numerous attempts to unite the Socialist Party with the SDF, the recruitment of SDF members and the defection of Socialist Party locals to the SDF, the repudiation of the "Popular Front" issue, the SDF's strong support for American participation in World War II, the SDF's attitude towards the 1940 and 1944 Presidential campaigns, the SDF's support for full employment and fair employment practices, the decline of the SDF in the late 1940s and early 1950s, and the steps taken towards the 1957 merger of the SDF and the Socialist Party. Most of the correspondence is from August Claessens, but there are numerous letters from Leo Meltzer, Algernon Lee, William Karlin, Sarah Limbach, Louis Waldman, Tom Mooney, Lena Morrow Lewis, Sonia Teitelman, Jasper McLevy, Roger Baldwin, Darlington Hoopes, Esther Friedman, James Oneal, George H. Goebel, and Norman Thomas. The SDF convention files (X:3 X:5) include press releases, organizational papers, correspondence, minutes, resolutions, and the SDF constitution and by laws.
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:1
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1953-Apr 1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, May 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous / General Items, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:2
  - National Convention: roll, press releases, organization, Apr 5, 1937-May 1, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:3
  - National Convention: Correspondence, Feb 22, 1937-Nov 16, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:4
  - National Convention: Minutes, Resolution, Constitution, May 1937 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:5
- Series II. State and International Files
  This series contains files on 42 state branches, the District of Columbia, and four countries, including Argentina (X:50), Canada (X:51), Mexico (X:52), and Switzerland (X:53). There is also a file on the armed forces which is located between the state and international files (X:49). The largest files in this part of the collection pertain to state branches in California (X:8), Florida (X:13), Illinois (X:15), Massachusetts (X:25), and the District of Columbia (X:46). Most of the other state branches as well as the foreign countries have relatively small files. The state branch files are arranged in alphabetical order according to the name of the state. The international files are also arranged in alphabetical order and are located after the state branch files. Items within each state branch and international file have been arranged in chronological order, with undated items placed at the end of the file.
  The contents of the state and international files relate primarily to such routine organizational matters as literature requests, membership and dues problems, and meetings. of special interest in these files are the papers of Mayor Jasper McLevy of Bridgeport, Connecticut (X:11). Other interesting items within these files are the Indiana State Executive Committee minutes (X:18) and the Pennsylvania State Executive Committee minutes (X:37).
  - Alabama, May 24, 1942-Oct 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:6
  - Arizona, Jan 6, 1937-Nov 27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:7
  - California, Jul 16, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:8
  - California, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - California, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - California, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - California, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - California, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - California, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Colorado, May 25, 1937-Dec 14, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:9
  - Connecticut: Correspondence, Feb 18, 1936-Dec 6, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:10
  - Connecticut, State Central Committee; Mayor Jasper McLevy, Materials and Clippings, Oct 24, 1937-Nov 8, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:11
  - Delaware, Apr 22, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:12
  - Florida, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 15, Frame X:13
  - Florida, 1940-1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Georgia, Jun 16, 1937-Feb 10, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:14
  - Idaho, Jul 1937-Nov 22, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:15
  - Illinois, Oct 15, 1936-Apr 21, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:16
  - Illinois, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Illinois, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Illinois, 1942-1944, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Indiana: Correspondence, Oct 26, 1936-Dec 28, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:17
  - Indiana, State Executive Committee Minutes, Jul 10, 1937-Jun 11, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:18
  - Iowa, Oct 7, 1936-Dec 5, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:19
  - Kansas, Dec 9, 1937-Jul 7, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:20
  - Kentucky, Nov 27, 1937-Oct 24, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:21
  - Louisiana, Sep 27, 1946-Nov 26, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:22
  - Maine, Jun 15, 1937-Feb 15, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:23
  - Maryland, Jul 26, 1937-Dec 24, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:24
  - Massachusetts, Jun 25, 1937-Apr 22, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:25
  - Massachusetts, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts, 1942-1944, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Michigan, Jan 20, 1937-Nov 25, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:26
  - Minnesota, May 1937-Feb 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:27
  - Missouri, Nov 25, 1936-Aug 19, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:28
  - Montana, Dec 1937-May 3 1939 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:29
  - Nevada, Dec 28, 1936-Dec 31, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:30
  - New Hampshire, Jul 6, 1938-May 4, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:31
  - North Carolina, Mar 1, 1939-Jan 29, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:32
  - Ohio, Oct 13, 1936-Nov 23, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:33
  - Oklahoma, Feb 2, 1938-Oct 16, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:34
  - Oregon, Dec 11, 1936-May 11, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:35
  - Pennsylvania: Corresp, Mar 17, 1936-Oct 28, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:36
  - Pennsylvania: [a] Local Berks County, Dues Report; [b] State Executive Committee Minutes, 1937, Feb 1940-Apr 1940 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:37
  - Rhode Island, Dec 28, 1936-Dec 8, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:38
  - South Dakota, Jul 1, 1937-Dec 11, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:39
  - Tennessee, Jan 22, 1938, May 4, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:40
  - Texas, Mar 1, 1939-Mar 7, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:41
  - Utah, Oct 23, 1936-Jun 10, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:42
  - Vermont, Dec 8, 1936-Nov 6, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:43
  - Virginia, Nov 2, 1937-Oct 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:44
  - Washington, Oct 25, 1937-Nov 25, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, FrameX:45
  - Washington, D.C., Jul 29, 1936-Jul 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:46
  - Washington, D.C., Aug 1938-Apr 1905 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Washington, D.C., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Washington, D.C., 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin, Apr 20, 1937-Oct 5, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:47
  - Wyoming, Mar 3, 1937-Jan 24, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:48
  - Armed Forces, Apr 22, 1941-May 31, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:49
  - Argentina, Sep 18, 1946-Oct 4, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:50
  - Canada, Jul 14, 1938-Dec 9, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:51
  - Mexico, Nov 12, 1937-Jan 13, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:52
  - Switzerland, May 4, 1938-May 30, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:53
- Series III. Jewish Socialist Verband Files
  The Jewish Socialist Verband Files contain a correspondence file (X:54) and a dues report (X:55). The items within these two files are arranged in chronological order. Besides several routine items, these papers contain information on the close relationship between this prominent socialist organization and the SDF.
  - Jewish Socialist Verband, Correspondence, Jun 7, 1937-Mar 11, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:54
  - Jewish Socialist Verband, Dues Report, Nov 15, 1937-Jan 1940 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:55
- Series IV. Committee Files
  This series contains 11 files which pertain to various SDF committees (X:56 X:66). The files are arranged in alphabetical order according to the name of the committee. Items within each committee file have been arranged in chronological order. One of the most interesting files in this section pertains to the Fred E. Beal case (X:56). In 1938 and 1939, the SDF conducted a vigorous campaign in support of the release of Fred E. Beal who was serving a 17 to 20 year prison term for being convicted of murdering a police chief during the 1929 Gastonia, North Carolina, textile workers strike. It was the SDF's belief that Beal was convicted because of his association with the Communist Party and his labor organizing activities. Another important file in this section pertains to the Spanish Workers Fund (X:65). The SDF organized the Spanish Workers Fund in the mid 1930s for the purpose of offering financial assistance, food, and medical supplies to the supporters of the Loyalists during the Spanish Civil War. Two other prominent files in this section pertain to the National Committee for the Protection and Welfare of Persecuted and oppressed European Victims (X:62) and the Women's Committee of the SDF (X:66).
  - Beal Committee, Feb 28, 1938-Jun 9, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:56
  - Camp Tamiment, Jun 8, 1937-Jun 25, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:57
  - Committee on Cooperatives, Oct 1937-Apr 1905 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:58
  - Committee on Cooperatives, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Cooperatives, Jan 2, 1940-Jun 3, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Labor Contracts, Jul 2, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:59
  - Organization Committee, May 22, 1937-Sep 16, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:60
  - Committee on Political Contacts, Jun 16, 1937-Sep 2, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:61
  - National Committee for the Protection and Welfare of Persecuted and Oppressed European Victims, Jun 14, 1937-Apr 25, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:62
  - Publicity Committee, Jun 14, 1937-Nov 28, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:63
  - Emergency Relief Committee, Jun 15, 1937-Jan 17, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:64
  - Spanish Workers Fund, Aug 4, 1936-Dec 30, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:65
  - Spanish Workers Fund, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Women's Committee, Dec 13, 1943-Jan 6, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 16, Frame X:66
- Series V: Financial Files
  This series contains accounts receivable (X:67), bequests (X:68), charters (X:69), mailing lists (X:70), miscellaneous papers (X:71), pledges (X:72), and pledge cards (X:73). These files are arranged in alphabetical order according to the document type. Items within each file are arranged in chronological order.
  - Accounts Receivable, Jun 28, 1938-Oct 1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:67
  - Bequests, Nov 30, 1938-Nov 29, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:68
  - Charters, Jul 12, 1937-Aug 1, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:69
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:70
  - Finances, Miscellaneous, Jun 14, 1937-Apr 17, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:71
  - Finances: Dues Pledges, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:72
  - Finances: Dues Pledges, 1939-1946 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Pledge cards, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 17, Frame X:73
  - Pledge cards, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Literature Files